<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="blogentry.xsl"?>
<blog
 xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xs:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="blog.xsd">

<blog_entries>
		
		<title>Sara: Guardian of her Troop!</title>
		
		<description>"Its a short but sweet story. Sara is our patrol dog that follows our platoon on every patrol. She originally came from saraposa prison, which is where we patrol daily, she followed us to our tiny COB, and has lived here ever since, and goes on every patrol with us ever since too. She's so sweet and loving and looks out for us and protects us, we all love her, my whole heartbreaker platoon. Thank You for your service! We will "NOT LEAVE SARA BEHIND". LETS GET HER TO THE LAND OF THE FREE, BECAUSE OF THE BRAVE! I think Sara may be the heartbreaker!I hope we can get her to the states.The primary mission of Puppy Rescue Mission is to raise funds assist various organizations which help soldiers bring home  from war. While PRM's primary mission is to assist soldiers and their furry friends, PRM will also, from time to time, assist an organization in rehoming a stray animal. In the event that there are funds remaining from the donations for this animal and any of the animals, The Puppy Rescue Mission Board of Directors will use the excess funds where necessary.
		</description>				
						
	</blog_entries>
	
	<blog_entries>
		
		<title>Stress is for Everyone!</title>
		
		<description>"It’s well known that post-traumatic stress is one of the major problems facing many veterans returning from the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. But now researchers are finding that a large number of military dogs may be grappling with the condition as well. By some estimates, more than 5 percent of the roughly 650 military dogs deployed by American combat forc...es are coming down with what researchers call canine PTSD, reports James Dao in The New York Times. Though veterinarians have long diagnosed behavioral problems in animals, the concept of canine PTSD is only about 18 months old, having come into vogue among military veterinarians who have been seeing patterns of troubling behavior among dogs exposed to explosions, gunfire and other combat-related violence in Iraq and Afghanistan. Like humans with the analogous disorder, different dogs show different symptoms. Some become hyper-vigilant. Others avoid buildings or work areas that they had previously been comfortable in. Some undergo sharp changes in temperament, becoming unusually aggressive with their handlers, or clingy and timid. Most crucially, many stop doing the tasks they were trained to perform.It’s not just military dogs. According to the article, a growing number of behaviorists say canine PTSD is also being seen in household pets that experience car accidents and other traumatic events. 
		</description>				
						
	</blog_entries>
		<blog_entries>
		
		<title>Crazed Cat Fax!!</title>
		
		<description>"A blog can be useful for countless reasons, so it's best to decide for yourself what your purpose in starting it is," she recommlasts. "It's certainly fantastic for both visibility and staying current in today's market, but how you position it is ultimately going to determine how it works for you."
		Blogging has been known as a way to share one’s thoughts about certain issues – personal or otherwise - although it seems like social networking sites are now the preferred venues for such purpose. Nevertheless, if you are a small business owner who wants to promote online, there are reasons why you should be blogging more, instead of focusing your energies solely on tweeting or updating your Facebook page status.
		Blogging can establish your authority. You can maximize your blog better if you will write less about your product/service but more about relevant information or your expert knowledge. This way, you are not only providing more value to your readers, but also showing that you are a reliable authority in your field.
		Blogging can help build your reputation. Potential customers oftentimes gauge a company’s reputation by what they read online. So instead of reading about your business elsewhere, why not offer them information straight from the source? Blogging provides you with an opportunity to establish your reputation and influence people’s impression of your professional identity.
		"A blog can be useful for countless reasons, so it's best to decide for yourself what your purpose in starting it is," she recommlasts. "It's certainly fantastic for both visibility and staying current in today's market, but how you position it is ultimately going to determine how it works for you."
		Blogging has been known as a way to share one’s thoughts about certain issues – personal or otherwise - although it seems like social networking sites are now the preferred venues for such purpose. Nevertheless, if you are a small business owner who wants to promote online, there are reasons why you should be blogging more, instead of focusing your energies solely on tweeting or updating your Facebook page status.
		Blogging can establish your authority. You can maximize your blog better if you will write less about your product/service but more about relevant information or your expert knowledge. This way, you are not only providing more value to your readers, but also showing that you are a reliable authority in your field.
		Blogging can help build your reputation. Potential customers oftentimes gauge a company’s reputation by what they read online. So instead of reading about your business elsewhere, why not offer them information straight from the source? Blogging provides you with an opportunity to establish your reputation and influence people’s impression of your professional identity.
		</description>				
						
	</blog_entries>
		<blog_entries>
		
		<title>Watching Whale Protections at Work!!!</title>
		
		<description>"As an environmental lawyer in Washington, D.C., much of my work involves the often invisible world of policy, laws, and court decisions. Every now and again, however, I have the incredible privilege of getting out to see the wildlife I work to protect. This past weekend, I got to do just that on a whale watching trip in one of the most important whale habitats on the East Coast of the United States—the waters off of Cape Cod, Massachusetts.

There were several whales in the water that day, but the most striking by far were the humpback mother and calf swimming alongside our boat. Locals told us that the mom was known as Mural, and that this was her third calf they’d identified over the years (as well as the first calf they’d seen this season). Not only did their beauty take my breath away as they gently rolled and swam close to each other and to our boat, but I was struck by how critically important our work to protect them really is. Those very whales I was watching might not have been there if it hadn’t been for our successful efforts to slow down ships and remove dangerous fishing gear from the water. And for the highly endangered North Atlantic right whales we heard were in the area (but couldn’t see because of extra protections that keep them free from disturbance by the public), it was enough to know they were there.
		
		</description>				
						
	</blog_entries>
</blog>